{"data":[{"question":"Jim gets up at half past seven everyday, has breakfast at eight o'clock, and starts works at half past nine.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"usually","b":"gets","c":"has","d":"on","answer":"4","explain":"- On-> at","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Holiday towns and fishing villages in the South - West are prepared to fight the oil pollution which is threatening local beaches.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"fishing","b":"prepared","c":"which","d":"local","answer":"2","explain":"- Prepared-> preparing","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Yesterday there was a collision in the English Channel between the S.P Titan, who is one of the biggest oil tankers in the world, and a Dutch cargo ship.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"was","b":"between","c":"who","d":"tankers","answer":"3","explain":"- Who-> which","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Helicopters rescued both crews, and nobody dies in the collision.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"rescued","b":"both","c":"dies","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"- Dies-> died","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Hundreds of small boats, which are carrying detergents, is spraying the oil.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of","b":"which","c":"carrying","d":"is","answer":"4","explain":"- Is-> are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"The Amazon forest, in Brazil, covers five million square kilometers - an area as bigger as the whole of Europe excluding Russia.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"covers","b":"million","c":"bigger","d":"excluding","answer":"3","explain":"- Bigger-> big","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"If the destruction of the forest continues at the same rate, there would be nothing left by the year 2005.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"If","b":"continues","c":"would","d":"left","answer":"3","explain":"- Would-> will","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Scientists says that the disappearance of the trees is already causing changes in the climate.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"says","b":"disappearance","c":"of","d":"in","answer":"1","explain":"- Says-> say","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Brunei is one of the smallest but most rich countries in the world.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"one","b":"smallest","c":"most rich","d":"in","answer":"3","explain":"- Most rich-> the richest","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"},{"question":"Most them think that Brunei is in the Middle East but it isn't.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"them","b":"that","c":"in","d":"isn't","answer":"1","explain":"- Most them-> most of them","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"22","subcategorylv2":"25","type":"1"}]}